So, I went on Facebook for the first
time today in a long time and and I
learned something. I I learned that my
wife is single. Uh so
yeah, I
I hit the like button.
My wife and I actually grew a lot closer
um since the pandemic. That's one
positive thing I will say that I in my
personal life through my wife and I grew
pretty tight because for a while there I
kind of lost my way a little bit. A
little cranky pants.
There was no entertainment. There was no
cruise ships. there was no work, you
know, and my wife really helped with my
self-esteem cuz she would say to me,
"Listen, I know you're not working and
you know, there's no shows and you're
bringing in no income and you really
can't help out with anything." So, I was
like, "All right, cool."
So, I got a little cranky, right?
So, one morning, my wife sits me down.
She goes, "Jeff, we have to talk." And
when your wife says that to you, it
never follows up with something like,
"We have to talk. You should really go
out with the guys more and go out
drinking."
She goes, "We have to talk." I GO,
"WHAT'S THE MATTER?" SHE GOES, "JEFF,
YOU CHANGED A LITTLE BIT. You're not the
same guy I married since the pandemic.
You're a little cranky." She goes, "You
raise your voice and you curse a lot."
And I said, "What the are you talking
about?"
I went, "Oh my goodness, you're right."
So she goes, "Listen, I want you to go
talk to somebody. I want you to go talk
to a therapist." She goes, "There's
nothing wrong with that. Everybody gets
a little therapy." She tells me, "If you
got something wrong with your tooth, you
go to the dentist. You got an eye
problem, you go to optometrist. You got
something going on, I want you to go
talk to somebody." So I agreed, you
know, because
uh she has a 401k and uh
doctor says, "Jeff, it's natural what
you're going through. I'm going to put
you on 15 milligrams a day of the
risopam."
See, she knows.
Make sure you read the pamphlet, Jeff,
with the side effects. Let me know if
you experience any of the side effects.
I said, "Okay, no problem." But I don't
tell my wife that they put me on
medication because I'm too manly. Macho
guy, you know. So, I go to CVS, I fill
the prescription, I I take the pills out
of the bag, I take the brochure, the
instructions, I throw it in the garbage.
I don't read nothing.
I start popping these pills. Yeah. Day
one,
two, three, four. But we're quarantined.
My anger is not being tested
till day five. Here we are, folks, in my
kitchen. 6:00 in the morning. I'm making
a cup of coffee. I take the coffee. I
put on the center island in the kitchen.
I turn into the cabinet to grab the
sugar. As I turn back, my elbow hits the
cup of coffee. The coffee smashes on the
floor. There's hot coffee and white
porcelain all over my leg. Now, normally
Jeff would have picked up the kitchen
bar stool and thrown it through the bay
window.
>> Yes. Sure,
BUT I WENT LIKE THIS.
HUH?
Would you look at that?
Like I I guess I got to make another cup
of coffee.
And I realized, wow, my goodness. I
didn't curse. I didn't break nothing. I
don't have to spackle anything tomorrow
morning, you know.
And I actually said this out loud in my
kitchen. And I went, "Wow." Huh?
Lorisa Pam. YEAH, I'M DOING COMMERCIALS
for nobody
in my kitchen.
just celebrated
19 years of marriage and uh yeah, it's
marriage is a gift. It truly is. It
really is. Some gifts you could return
and some you can't. But um
marriage is a gift.
I'm in an interracial marriage and I I
say that proudly cuz I do think the
world's a little little messed up right
now, you know, and some people could be
mean. I never realized it, you know, cuz
my wife and I are different, you know.
We grew up on different sides of the
tracks, you know what I'm saying?
Different skin tone, different beliefs,
but we fell in love. I obviously uh am
Irish and um my wife is an Italian
now.
I don't know.
I'm with the family 20 years. I still
don't know if I'm accepted. You know, I
didn't get a union card yet. I don't
know what's going on. Right.
Love Italian people. I do. I knew I
wanted to marry my wife when I first met
her, you know, but I get nervous in
front of women. I always did, ladies,
because I have so much respect for you.
I never know what to say to a woman.
That's why I was the athlete or the
funny guy in front of women. I I start
to sweat. I stutter. People make
donations.
It
It gets embarrassing, right?
So, I went up to my wife and I did
really good to him. Made eye contact.
They go, "How you doing? My name's
Jeff." And um I I I I was I I She goes,
"Don't be nervous." She goes, "Tell me
something about you." So yeah, genius. I
went like this. Uh my name's Jeff and uh
my mind's like, "Say something." I'm
like, "Uh, my name's Jeff and I'm Irish.
That's what I said." And just like you
folks, no reaction at all
cuz YOU DID THE RIGHT THING. THAT'S NOT
IMPRESSIVE TO TELL AN ITALIAN WOMAN. I
mean, I'M NOT MOCKING MY FELLOW
IRISHMAN, but what are you going to brag
about
to an Italian woman?
Hey, uh, I'm Irish.
Do you like cabbage?
DO YOU LIKE ALL YOUR FOOD BOILED WITH NO
SEASONING EVER IN YOUR LIFE?
>> HEY, how would you like an alcoholic
father-in-law?
Yeah, we all have one of them. Um,
people say you tell the truth up there.
I go, I absolutely tell the truth up
there. My family is nuts.
If they were ever going to make a movie
or a documentary about my life, they'd
have to get the proper actors to portray
the members of my family.
So, if you keep this visual in your
mind, you'll be right in the living room
for the whole meeting of the parents,
right? I said to my wife when I first
met her, I go, "You know, I really like
your company. I travel a lot. Maybe you
and your family should come to my house
to meet myself and my family." She goes,
"Really? My whole family?" I go, "Yes,
bring your whole family." Yeah. 72 cars
pull up on Saturday, right?
I panic because the difference in family
is so obvious, you know. My parents,
your typical Irish parents, you know. My
dad's a good guy, hardworking guy. We
all have a flaw. My dad's biggest flaw
is
he he curses. He uses curse words as an
adjective. You know, he doesn't mean
anything by it, but you know, growing up
in a bar, I guess you pick up bad
habits. MY MOTHER'S TOTAL OPPOSITE. MY
MOTHER'S ALWAYS IN CHURCH. MY mother's
always praying. She's an incredible
woman. My mom, she's an amazing woman.
She actually watches the news and makes
a list of people to pray for. I mean,
she's amazing. I'm not even kidding you.
My mother doesn't even curse. How do you
live in New Jersey and not curse 15
times a day?
If my mother gets mad rather than curse,
you know what she'll do? She'll spell
the curse word out
in the middle of the sentence because I
guess she thinks the Lord can't spell.
Hey.